coilart.net 2019-03-23

# Privacy notice - CoilART | Discover your flavor—Mage mech mod

Coilart.net knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust. Protection of your personal data, processing and use when visiting our website is a matter of importance to us. We, therefore, take all necessary precaution to ensure the information given us by you remains confidential. This privacy policy outlines the types, uses and disclosure of the information collected and the methods of collecting information.

**Information Collected**

Coilart.net collect many kinds of information in order to operate effectively, customize your experience and provide you the best products, and services. Some of the information collected, you provide directly to us by filling out our forms while some of it we get by observing how you interact with our Products and Services. We believe it is important to protect and treat the information with care. Below, we describe in detail what information we collect and how Coilart.net collects it.

We observe and remain in accordance with the Children’s Privacy Protection Act and any other applicable laws.

**Registration and Signing In**

You may be required to provide information about yourself such as name, birthdate, and address when you register an account with http://www.coilart.net. To access some of our services, you will need to log in into your account with your username and/or email address and a password. During the use of our websites and services, we automatically collect information that tells http://www.coilart.net how you interact with our services.

**How we collect your information**

We use a number of methods in the collection of information about how you use our website. We do this so that we can improve our products and services. These methods are:

Web forms which you use during registration

Weblogging enables us to collect information that your browser sends to every website you visit. For example, your IP address.

Technologies such as cookies too, enable us to collect information from you.

**Use of Personal Information**

Coilart.net uses the personal information mostly for technical administration of our website and to improve, and personalize the products and services we offer. Some other uses of the personal information collected are described below:

Managing the accounts registered with us effectively

Administering the periodic and voluntary surveys

Sending emails sometimes. The emails will provide the user with the option of unsubscribing from any future emails that they may not wish to receive.

**Disclosure of Information Collected**

Information about our members is important to us and we do not disclose it to any third parties without your consent. The information will be kept within the Central System and only provided during special circumstances such as when required by law to do so in compliance with a Privacy Act. We will not be able to control how third parties use your personal information once your consent is obtained. Explained below, are situations which may require your consent to release your personal information;

**Third-Party Service Providers:**

Sometimes Coilart.net seek out the services of other companies and websites to perform certain tasks on our behalf. To access some of these services, the third parties may need some information which we will only disclose to them upon obtaining your consent.

**Promotional Offers:**

We send some of our members with offers for promotional purposes. We do not give your personal details to these third parties but when you win a prize, your consent may be required so that the prizes can be processed and released to you.

**Affiliated Businesses:**

Sometimes we may offer products that are co-branded with our affiliates or joint offerings to you. To obtain such products, we may need to obtain your consent to provide personal information to the third parties.

**Cookies**

We and some of our third-party service providers use “cookies.” A “cookie” is a small text file written by an Internet server to a website user’s browser where information is exchanged between them, and which is stored on a computer’s hard drive to allow us to recognize and track users on the Website to assist us in providing our customers with a productive online experience. Cookies enable us to store information about your use of the Website, such as the areas you visit and the length of your stay. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies and can be reset by using the ‘Help’ portion of the toolbar to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. Should you choose to disable any cookies associated with the Website, you will not be able to take full advantage of all the Website’s features, but you should be able to navigate the Website without difficulty.

**Changes to Our Policy**

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, you can always contact [Coilart customer Care](http://www.coilart.net/contact/) by sending us an email message
